foodafactoflife.org.uk 2006-10-23

# Teacher Area

The Food - a fact of life website has been developed by the British Nutrition Foundation (BNF). BNF has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to users' privacy.

## Information we collect and how it is used

Your IP address is automatically collected when you visit the site because your IP address needs to be recognised by the server. We use your IP address to record general site usage information and browsing preferences, but not to track your individual visit. We do not identify individual users in this sort of research. By using this website and by submitting information to us via this website you give your consent that all your personal data collected by us via this website may be processed by us for the purposes set out in the following data privacy policy.

You have the facility to submit a limited amount of personal contact data about yourself in the course of accessing our site. These contact details are held on our database and used exclusively by the BNF for the purpose of sending you information on current and future information about the services and publications and any other services described on this website, and/or implementing any other requests or suggestions you may have made.

Except as required for the purposes of hosting this site, we will not pass your information to any third party. This site is hosted by Hosting UK. They will use your information only for administration of the site and will not pass your details to anybody.

## Cookies

We may also store information about you using cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you visit our site in future. We do this to manage your use of the site more efficiently and to record any user preferences.

Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at [ www.AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). Please note that by deleting our cookies or disabling future cookies you may not be able to access certain areas or features of our site.

## Data access and corrections

Upon receipt of your written request, we will disclose to you your personal data held by us, we shall correct or delete inaccurate details. We regularly delete data which is no longer required. Website related requests can be made by email to [postbox@nutrition.org.uk](mailto:postbox@nutrition.org.uk)

## Update our records/Remove your details

If you have any other questions about the use of your personal information, please contact the BNF at the address below.

## Registered Company information

BNF is a registered charity (Charity Number 251681 Company Number 898651) whose registered office is at:

British Nutrition Foundation, High Holborn House, 52-54 High Holborn, London WC1V 6RQ  
Tel: 020 7404 6504  
Fax: 020 7404 6747  
Email: [postbox@nutrition.org.uk](mailto:postbox@nutrition.org.uk)

The company hosting this site is Hosting UK (Company number 3629948) whose registered office is at:

Hosting UK  
Internet Engineering Limited, Richard House, Winckley Square, Preston, PR1 3HP  

Click here to return to the previous page.
